{
  " Paperwork": [
    {
      "question": "Do you think an internship can be considered professional experience?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No", "Neutral"],
      "correct": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "In a CV, the chronological order of mentioned dates is:",
      "options": ["From oldest to most recent", "From most recent to oldest", "Mixed"],
      "correct": "From most recent to oldest"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where can you mention your obtained certifications?",
      "options": ["Academic training", "Additional training", "Computer skills"],
      "correct": "Additional training"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you think a single CV can be valid for all positions?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No", "Neutral"],
      "correct": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "To trigger an interview you need to:",
      "options": ["Mention false diplomas, skills...", "Be honest and clear in your paperwork", "Neutral"],
      "correct": "Be honest and clear in your paperwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "Do you think the cover letter can replace the CV?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No", "Neutral"],
      "correct": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "Choose the correct order of the following sections in a cover letter:",
      "options": ["I know myself, I know you, let's meet", "Let's meet, I know you, I know myself", "I know you, I know myself, let's meet"],
      "correct": "I know myself, I know you, let's meet"
    },
    {
      "question": "Should you mention information about the company (date of creation, field of activity...) in a cover letter?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No", "Neutral"],
      "correct": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Should you include a photo in a cover letter?",
      "options": ["Yes", "No", "Neutral"],
      "correct": "No"
    },
    {
      "question": "The CV and cover letter should be sent in format:",
      "options": ["PDF", "Word", "JPG"],
      "correct": "PDF"
    }
  ]
}
